### JIANGHAO LI

500 Smith Level Rd 27510, NC, USA +1 (919) 995-0369 li jianghao@lilly.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jianghaoli/

### **PROFILE**

A logical, responsive and task-focused biostatistics PhD who excels at analytical problem solving. Extensive experience in clinical trials, from trial design to data analysis. Current research focuses on survival analysis and group sequential studies. Interested in statistical research in healthcare industry.

### **EDUCATION**

# DUKE UNIVERSITY, Durham, NC

PhD in Biostatistics, 2020

Dissertation: "Sample size calculation for comparing distributions of correlated time-to-event endpoint"

### PEKING UNIVERSITY, Beijing, China

Bachelor of Science, Statistics and Probability, July, 2015

Thesis: "Statistical Analysis of Standardize Infertility Treatment Level in China"

## Bachelor of Art, Economics July, 2015

Double major in economics at China Center for Economic Research (CCER)

### **EXPERIENCE**

Eli Lilly, Indianapolis, IN

2020-present

### Research Scientist – Statistics

- Work as lead statistician in various clinical trials for diabetes
- Conduct statistical research that is applicable to advancement of drug development

Sanofi, Boston, MA Statistics PhD intern 2019 summer

Proposed a two stage optimal design for selection and assessment of agreement of the best instruments with the existence of gold standard

# **DUKE CLINICAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE, Durham, NC**

2017-2020

### Research Assistant

- Worked as lead statistician on several projects in ISCHEMIA trial. Proposed non-parametric estimator of days alive and out of hospital (DAOH), and analyzed the effect of age and OMT goal attainment on ischemic heart disease
- Performed Bayesian network meta analysis to compare the safety and effectiveness of different antithrombotic treatment strategies for patients with AF and ACS and/or undergoing PC
- Worked on jointly modeling HIV viral load and CD4 count over time, and performed MCEM for inference
- Worked on a project on assessing the quality of life by EQ-5D and mortality in patients with ischemic cardiomyopathy randomized to CABG or medical therapy
- Served as lead statistician in projects analyzing trends in pulmonary and solid organ transplant studies
- Helped to design a phase IV clinical trial for a diabetes treatment

# **DUKE UNIVERSITY,** Department of Biostatistics and Bioinformatics, Durham, NC

2015-2016

# Teaching Assistant

- Assisted four graduate-level courses as a teaching assistant with about 30 students in each class
- Held office hours for students, answer questions about lectures, evaluate and grade assignments

### PRICEWATERHOUSECOOPERS (PwC), Beijing, China

2013

## Intern in Advisory Department

- Wrote the report of investment appraisal and business case development, including hard to quantify benefits
- Analyzed shareholder value impacts, and improved investor communications
- Collected information and adopted market approach in appraising real estate

## **PUBLICATIONS**

Jianghao Li, Sin-Ho Jung, "Group sequential testing for cluster randomization trials with time-to-event endpoint", Biometrics, 2021. https://doi.org/10.1111/biom.13498

Jianghao Li, Sin-Ho Jung, "Sample size calculation for cluster randomization trials with a time-to-event endpoint", Statistics in Medicine, 2020. https://doi.org/10.1002/sim.8683

**Jianghao Li**, Shein-Chung Chow, "Statistical Evaluation of the Scaled Criterion for Drug Interchangeability", *Journal of Biopharmaceutical Statistics*, 2016. <a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1080/10543406.2016.1265538">http://dx.doi.org/10.1080/10543406.2016.1265538</a>

Jianghao Li, Shein-Chung Chow, "Confidence Region Approach for Assessing Bioequivalence and Biosimilarity Accounting for Heterogeneity of Variability", Journal of Probability and Statistics, 2015. http://dx.doi.org/10.1155/2015/298647

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

R, SAS, Python, Latex, MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint Computer:

Language: English, Chinese